{"response_code":0,"results":[{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Centripedal force is an apparent force that acts outward on a body moving around a center, arising from the body&#039;s inertia.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"A defibrillator is used to start up a heartbeat once a heart has stopped beating.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Sugar contains fat.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"An average human can go two weeks without water.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Steel is an alloy of Iron and Carbon.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Psychology is the science of behavior and mind.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"The Doppler effect applies to light.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]}
